so hello everybody my name is Mills
大家好，我叫米尔斯
oopah I'm a software developer at DNA
oopah我是DNA的软件开发人员
stack where we've built a called
堆栈，我们在其中建立了一个
platform for genomics our platform is
基因组学平台，我们的平台是
written primarily in Java so we've
主要是用Java编写的，所以我们已经
started looking into what's new in Java
开始研究Java的新功能
9 and I thought it would be interesting
9，我认为这很有趣
to share this information so the goal of
分享这些信息，因此目标
this talk is to go through a couple of
这个演讲是要经历几个
my favorite API in Java 9 we're not
我最喜欢的Java 9 API，不是
going to talk about modularity or
要谈论模块化或
language improvements I feel like that
我感觉语言得到了改善
has been sufficiently covered elsewhere
在其他地方已被充分覆盖
well you're going to focus on our
好吧，您将专注于我们
library api's and particularly smaller
库api，尤其小
api api's that don't get get that much
api api不会得到那么多
emphasis or that I think are underrated
强调或我认为被低估了
or just API is that make it easier for
或只是API使得它更容易
it to write cleaner code so we're going
编写更干净的代码，所以我们要
to take a look at the existing API
看一下现有的API
that's the collections API streams API
这就是集合API流API
and completable future api's and the
以及可完成的未来api和
improvements that they got in the latest
他们最新的改进
release of the java platform as well as
Java平台以及
the new api is in the release and that's
新的api已发布，那就是
the stack volker process handle and HTTP
堆栈Volker进程句柄和HTTP
to client and that's as far as I'm gonna
给客户，这就是我要的
go with slides I feel like the smaller
和幻灯片一起去，我觉得更小
api's are best explained using examples
最好用示例解释api
so we're just gonna do a live demo and
所以我们要做一个现场演示，
we're going to write all the examples in
我们将在其中编写所有示例
J shell and basically for each API I
J shell和基本上每个API
would like to show how this was
想展示这是怎么回事
approached prior to Java 9 will API so
在Java 9之前会采用API
we had available then and how this can
我们当时有空，如何可以
be done better in July 9 so I hope you
在7月9日做得更好，所以我希望你
can all see this what you can see here
都可以看到这里的内容
is J shell which is the tool oh really
是J shell，真的是工具哦
yeah can we do something about the
是的，我们可以做些什么
lights here
灯在这里
has this not sure how to be honest
有这个不确定如何诚实
yeah I think we're we're stuck with this
是的，我想我们被困在了这里
is this readable yeah okay great okay so
这是可读性吗很好很好所以
J shell is a tool bundled with the JDK
J Shell是JDK附带的工具
and it's essentially Java implementation
它本质上是Java实现
of ripe old read eval print loop so it's
成熟的旧读取eval打印循环的原因是
a tool that loops continuously reads
不断循环读取的工具
your input evaluates it prints out the
您的输入评估它会打印出
output so it's basically similar to
输出，所以它基本上类似于
common line interfaces that you're used
常用的线路接口
to from other languages such as groovy
到其他语言，例如groovy
Scala Python they all had that before
Scala Python他们以前都有过
and finally Java is getting one as well
最后Java也得到了
it's a really good tool for when you
这是一个非常好的工具，当您
need to try something very quickly so
需要很快尝试一些东西
it's good for prototyping just exploring
这只是探索原型的好方法
you api's or learning the language if
您的api或学习语言，如果
you're new to java the main thing that
您是Java的新手，
you need to know about J shell is that
您需要了解的J Shell是
it accepts two types of inputs there are
它接受两种类型的输入
snippets
片段
so the actual Java code that you want to
所以您想要的实际Java代码
evaluate and there's commands to the
评估，并有命令
actualization tool which always start
总是启动的实现工具
with a slash and we're going to show a
带有斜线，我们将显示一个
couple of these for this talk but let's
在本次演讲中，我们将其中几个
start with something really simple I'm
从一个非常简单的事情开始
just gonna do one plus one here you can
只要在这里做一加一就可以
see two interesting things here first of
首先在这里看到两个有趣的东西
all one plus one is two
一加一是二
second of all two was assigned to
两者中的第二个被分配给
something called dollar one here and the
这里叫做一美元的东西
other one is an implicit variable that
另一个是隐式变量
J's all created for me and it does that
J都是为我创造的，它做到了
whenever you have an expression that you
每当你有一个表达，你
don't assign to anything I could have of
不要分配任何我可以拥有的
course created my own variable I could
当然创建了我自己的变量
have just something she's done something
她刚刚做某事
like this and this is the name of the
像这样，这就是
variable X and you've seen the first
变量X，您已经看到了第一个
shortcuts that I used here Michelle has
我在这里使用Michelle的快捷方式
a couple of these shape tab and we
几个这样的形状标签，我们
infers a type of variable from the
从中推断出变量的类型
expression and then introduces a new
表达式，然后引入一个新的
variable of that type I'm going to use
我将要使用的那种类型的变量
this extensively for the talk jeschill
这广泛用于谈论jeschill
also features standard tab completion
还具有标准的制表符完成功能
that you're used to from other shells so
你习惯从其他壳
I can take advantage of this where I
我可以在这里利用我的优势
would say print out my variable
会说打印出我的变量
something like this and that's do so
这样的事情就是这样
there's a couple of syntactic shortcuts
有几个语法捷径
as well you
还有你
Oh
哦
that's good great yes so these are
很好，很好，所以这些是
syntactic shortcuts you've noticed that
您已经注意到的语法快捷方式
I didn't need to read my expression in
我不需要阅读我的表情
anything it's just one plus one like
任何只是一加一的东西
this I also need to didn't need to put a
这我也不需要放一个
semicolon at the end of my statement I
我发言结束时的分号
wouldn't need to worry about catching
不用担心赶上
checked exceptions and a couple of
检查异常和几个
things like that so this brings us to
这样的事情，所以这使我们
the first command and that's worse which
第一个命令，更糟的是
simply lists all the variables that I've
只需列出我拥有的所有变量
declared similarly to days I can type
声明与我可以输入的日期类似
the methods and classes in J shell and
J Shell中的方法和类以及
there's the respective commands for that
有相应的命令
that's it super types but of course I
这就是超级类型，但是我当然
don't have anything here at this point
目前没有任何东西
there's also lists that lists all my
还有一个列表列出了我所有的
snippets and Rochelle has this prefix
片段和Rochelle具有此前缀
mention going on so as long as you
提到只要你
specify a unique prefix of a command it
指定命令的唯一前缀
can actually find the command and
可以实际找到命令并
execute it so I could have done just
执行它，这样我就可以完成
something like this and the last meant
这样的东西和最后的意思
here is command help that just gives you
这是只是给您的命令帮助
information about everything else that
有关其他所有信息
you can do with your channel that's
您可以使用自己的频道
pretty much all that you need to know J
您几乎所有需要知道的J
was a tool is extremely easy to figure
是一个非常容易理解的工具
out so let's move on to the first API
出来，让我们继续第一个API
the first on the list our convenience
清单上的第一个方便
factoring methods for collections and
集合的保理方法和
Java 9 makes it really easy to create
Java 9使创建起来非常容易
immutable collections of small sizes
小规模的不可变集合
this is something that was relatively
这是相对的
tedious to do prior to Java 9 and I'm
在Java 9之前做起来很乏味，而我
sure everybody knows Israel if I wanted
确保每个人都知道以色列，如果我想
to create a set for example I would have
例如创建一个集
to do something like this let's say a
做这样的事情，让我们说一个
set of string and let's call it a set
一组字符串，我们称之为一组
then I would add a couple of elements
然后我要添加几个元素
let's say like this and then to make it
让我们说这样，然后使它
immutable I would wrap it in an in a
一成不变，我会把它包装在
modifiable set like this
像这样的可修改集
and there are a couple of issues with
而且有几个问题
this approach first of all it's pretty
这种方法首先很漂亮
verbose so you have static variables you
详细，所以您有静态变量
need to do a static initializer block
需要做一个静态的初始化块
that's not really convenient
那不是很方便
there's also performance overhead this
还有性能开销
is no really an immutable collection
真的不是一个不变的集合
it's more like an immutable view of an
它更像是一个不变的观点
existing collection so if I kept the
现有的收藏，所以如果我保留
reference to the original set I would
参考我会的原始设置
still be able to modify it and there's
仍然能够修改它，并且
performance overhead associated with
与之相关的性能开销
supporting mutability not to mention all
支持可变性，更不用说全部了
the extra objects that I had to create
我必须创建的额外对象
in the process just to get to the
在过程中只是为了
immutable collection but that's much
一成不变的收藏，但很多
easier in Gemini on Java 9 has static
在Java 9的Gemini上更容易拥有静态
factory methods on all the many
许多工厂方法
interfaces listed on map I can easily
我可以轻松地在地图上列出的界面
create a collection like this it's
创建这样的集合
overall with a bunch of times 12 to be
总的来说是12倍
exact so it's always 0 to 10 arguments
确切的，因此它始终是0到10个参数
and then the last one is power arcs and
最后一个是电弧
the reason it's done this way it's
这样做的原因是
because there's performance overhead
因为有性能开销
associated with creating the array to
与创建数组相关联
back up the fire arc so if you're
备份电弧，如果你是
creating reasonably small collections
创建合理的小馆藏
which presumably is going to satisfy
大概会满足
vast majority of use cases you want to
您想要的绝大多数用例
avoid this panel thing so I can create a
避免这种面板的事情，所以我可以创建一个
list just easily like this let's call
像这样轻松地列出
this a list and then if I try to add
这是一个列表，然后如果我尝试添加
something to this list you can see that
在此列表中，您可以看到
really it's immutable it's gonna throw
真的是一成不变的
an exception
一个例外
similarly you like to try to get the
同样，您喜欢尝试获取
class it's going to tell me that
上课会告诉我
something immutable but an interesting
不变但有趣的东西
thing to note here is these immutable
这里要注意的是这些一成不变的
classes are not really a part of the
类不是真正的一部分
public API so we can only rely on the
公共API，因此我们只能依靠
interface here and similarly the factory
在这里和工厂相似的界面
methods are methods on the interface so
方法是接口上的方法，因此
they're not inherited you cannot invoke
他们不是继承的，你不能调用
them for an implementing class so this
他们为实施类，所以这
is pretty much the only way to create
是几乎唯一的创建方法
this list and that's just a nice design
这个列表，那只是一个不错的设计
pattern to point out so first set it's
要指出的模式，因此首先设置
pretty much the same thing for a map
地图几乎是一样的
it's a bit different though for a map we
虽然对于地图我们有点不同
have eleven methods here so it's always
这里有11种方法，所以总是
a zero to ten elements or in this case
零到十个元素，或者在这种情况下
twenty because you always specify key
二十，因为您总是指定密钥
and value interchangeably there's no VAR
和价值可互换，没有VAR
arc version of this methods and that's
这种方法的弧形版本，那就是
because keys and values can have
因为键和值可以有
different types and you cannot have two
不同的类型，你不能有两个
arguments the same method so what
参数相同的方法又是什么
they've done with this is actually
他们已经完成了这实际上是
created a separate method which takes
创建了一个单独的方法
just one var arc of my entries so
我输入的内容只有一个
to take advantage of this I could just
利用这一点，我可以
create a map doing something like this
创建一个像这样的地图
and I have a map where key is an integer
我有一张地图，其中键是整数
and value is a string and that's pretty
和值是一个字符串，这很漂亮
much all there is to know about these
关于这些，有很多了解
factory methods so it's just a really
工厂方法，所以这只是一个真正的
nice convenience feature collections
便利功能集
play very nicely when the streams API
串流API时播放效果非常好
which was introduced in Java eight and
在Java 8中引入
streams learned a couple of new tricks
流学习了一些新技巧
in Java night as well so the first
在Java之夜也是如此
feature that I would like to talk about
我想谈谈的功能
here is a job while and take well
这是一会儿的工作，要做好
methods so let's just let's just go back
方法，让我们回过头来
and have a look at what we could do in
看看我们可以做什么
Java
爪哇
eight it created a stream of ins
八个它创建了一个ins流
something like this let's say zero to
像这样说零
nine and then just printed I'm just
九，然后只是打印，我只是
gonna use a quick method reference here
将在这里使用快速方法参考
and I have numbers 0 to 9 what I also
我有0到9的数字
had available in java 8 were methods
在Java 8中可用的方法
lina done skip so i could do something
莉娜（Lina）跳过了，所以我可以做点什么
like this limit 5 which gives me the
就像这个极限5，这给了我
first 5 elements of the stream and a
流的前5个元素和一个
complimentary method scape gives me the
免费方法scape给了我
rest of the string so that was good but
其余的字符串，所以很好，但是
the problem with this was that in
问题是
certain situations you don't know this
在某些情况下你不知道
number beforehand you just know that you
事先号码，你只知道你
want to keep taking elements while a
想要继续吸收元素的同时
certain condition is met and that at
满足一定条件
some point you have enough but there
有一点你有足够的，但那里
wasn't really an easy way to express
并不是真正简单的表达方式
this in java age in general 9 however we
这在Java时代一般9，但是我们
have take well in job well methods so i
有很好的工作方法，所以我
can specify something like this let's
可以指定类似这样的内容
say X is less than 5 and a complimentary
说X小于5并且是免费的
operation job while so these are kind of
操作作业，而这些都是
like versions of limited escape that
像有限逃生的版本
take a predicate instead of a fixed
采取谓词而不是固定式
value and it's just really nice to have
价值，拥有它真的很棒
this here another new method here is the
这是这里的另一种新方法是
method iterate let's take a look at it
方法迭代让我们看一下
you can see that our two versions of
您可以看到我们的两个版本
this method the first one was available
这种方法第一个可用
in Java age the second one was added in
在Java时代，第二个在
Java 9 and the difference is the
Java 9和不同之处在于
predicate here so let's take an example
谓词在这里，让我们举一个例子
let's say let's say I want to list all
假设我想列出所有
the even number
偶数
that are less than 100 now a very naive
少于100现在非常幼稚
approach to do this in Java age would be
在Java时代做到这一点的方法是
to do something like this I'm gonna
做这样的事情，我要
iterate from zero let's increment by one
从零开始迭代，让我们加一
by two and then I'm going to print all
两点，然后我将打印所有
of these and the method reference here
这些和方法参考这里
just like this and you can see that it
就像这样，你可以看到它
kind of worked up not really because I
有点工作不是因为我
forgot a filter so I would filter this
忘记过滤器，所以我要过滤这个
let's say I think I said 100 I can do
假设我说我可以做到100
this and this almost works and the
这和这几乎有效，并且
reason this doesn't work even though it
即使它无法工作的原因
seems like a very simple example is that
似乎很简单的例子是
I did filter the first 100 elements here
我确实在这里过滤了前100个元素
but I created an infinite stream so
但是我创建了一个无限流
after a while the stream kept going at
过了一会儿，溪流不断
some point it went over and suddenly all
有些时候它过去了，突然之间
my integers were less than 100 there
我的整数小于100
wasn't really a good way of expressing
并不是真正表达的好方法
this boundary condition in July 8 but in
这个边界条件是在7月8日，但在
Java 9
Java 9
I can actually easily do this I'm just
我实际上可以轻松做到这一点
gonna remove the filter here I can add
要在这里删除过滤器，我可以添加
another condition here something like
这里的另一个条件是
this this is going to work correctly so
这将正常工作，所以
if you look at it it reads essentially
如果你看它本质上读
like a four cycle and that's basically
像四个周期，基本上
what it is it's like a stream e5 version
就像流e5版本一样
of 4 so just a really really nice handy
之4，所以真的非常好用
feature here now the last method that I
现在在这里介绍我的最后一种方法
wanted to mention here is method of
想在这里提到的是
knowledge
知识
so in Java 8 I could create streams of
所以在Java 8中，我可以创建
certain specific elements using a
某些特定元素使用
factory method I could do something like
工厂方法我可以做类似的事情
this which would give me a stream
这会让我流
containing a single element and an
包含一个元素和一个
element is one what I couldn't do is
元素是我不能做的一个
something like this which makes sense
这样的事情很有意义
because you don't want to have knowledge
因为你不想有知识
in your streams
在你的流中
however in German I can do off nullable
但是用德语我可以取消可为空
pass now it'll actually gives me a
现在通过它实际上会给我一个
stream and if I have a look at it and
流，如果我看看它，
call the method count it tells me that
调用方法计数，它告诉我
it's actually an empty stream so Gemini
它实际上是一条空河，所以双子座
is smart enough to treat now as kind of
足够聪明，现在可以将其视为
an empty stream so where is it useful it
空流，它在哪里有用
basically makes integration better so
基本上使集成更好
you're writing along streams and you
你正在沿着流写作，你
have a
有一个
of chained operations especially maps at
连锁经营，尤其是地图
some point you're gonna end up with
有些事情你会最终
nulls and you will need to filter result
null，您将需要过滤结果
because you don't wanna have them in
因为你不想让他们进来
your streams you don't want to have Mel
你不想拥有梅尔
upon your exceptions so at some point
在您的例外情况下，在某些时候
you will have a block with an e
你将有一个带有e的方块
statement or a ternary operator that
语句或三元运算符
gets rid of these nails and that's just
摆脱这些指甲，那仅仅是
not really nice coat you have so this
你的外套不是很漂亮
allows you to get rid of those null
允许您摆脱那些空值
checks just a nice convenience feature
检查只是一个很好的便利功能
there another API the plays really
还有另一个戏剧
nicely with streams is the completable
与流很好地是可完成的
future api completable futures basically
未来api可完成的期货
provide framework for a synchronous
提供同步框架
programming in Java they were introduced
Java编程介绍
in in Java 8 and they're kind of build
在Java 8中，它们是一种构建
around the class called completable
围绕类称为完成
future and as the name would suggest
未来，顾名思义
this is essentially a future that can be
这本质上是可以
explicitly completed so what this is
明确完成，所以这是什么
used for is you typically use this to
用于的是您通常使用它来
model tasks particularly a synchronous
建模任务，尤其是同步任务
tasks in a bigger computation that
在更大的计算中完成任务
consists of many tasks so you can change
包含许多任务，因此您可以更改
the status and the value of the future
未来的地位和价值
and you also have IP is for creating
而且您还有IP用于创建
dependencies between futures so we can
期货之间的依赖性，因此我们可以
express things like ok when this feature
使用此功能时表示可以
is done triggered this action so let's
完成触发了此操作，所以让我们
just have a look at the really basic
看看真正的基础
functionality here you can create a new
功能，您可以在此处创建新
future let's say future of string so
未来，说字符串的未来，所以
let's call it CF then I can complete the
我们称之为CF，然后我就可以完成
future with a value it might get a
具有价值的未来可能会得到
string and you can see that now the
字符串，您现在可以看到
feature is completed normally and if I
功能正常完成，如果我
try to extract the value it's actually
尝试提取实际的价值
going to give me that value so what
会给我那种价值，那又如何
happens if I don't complete the future
如果我不完成未来会发生
let's reinitialize this here and I'm
让我们在这里重新初始化，我
just going to call the get method direct
只是直接调用get方法
thing and you can see that in this case
事情，你可以看到在这种情况下
it just keeps blocking and this so it's
它只是一直在阻塞，所以
essentially waiting for somebody else to
本质上是在等别人
complete the feature from different
完成不同功能
threads and that's basically how you
线程，这基本上就是你
synchronize using this constructor you
使用此构造函数进行同步
can also complete the future
也可以完成未来
exceptionally which allows you to give
可以让您付出
it a file in this case I'm just going to
在这种情况下它是一个文件
pass any legal state exception for
通过任何合法的州例外
example and now if I try to obtain the
示例，现在，如果我尝试获取
value of the future
未来的价值
it's actually going to fail with that
这实际上会失败
exception they gave it so that's kind of
他们给的例外，所以有点
the basic functionality around
基本功能
completable futures Java 9 introduced a
可完成的期货Java 9引入了
bunch of things quite a few actually
一堆东​​西实际上很多
completable future is a pretty big class
可完成的未来是一个很大的类
almost three thousand lines of code and
近三千行代码和
it has a bunch of methods and a bunch of
它有一堆方法和一堆
public methods as well and quite a few
公共方法也很多
of these were added in Java 9 most of
其中大多数是在Java 9中添加的
them are not very exciting it's mostly
他们不是很兴奋，主要是
stuff regular methods factory methods
常规方法工厂方法
methods that make it easier for you to
使您更轻松的方法
subclass computable future and stuff
子类可计算的未来和东西
like that there are three however them
像这样，三个
really excited about and Gemini and
真的很兴奋，双子座和
basically provided a new way of
基本上提供了一种新的方式
completing futures based on a time out
根据超时完成期货
so in Java nine I can do something
所以在Java 9中我可以做点什么
something like this let's reinitialize
这样的事情让我们重新初始化
this here and can call complete on time
在这里，可以按时致电完成
out which takes a value turned out and
拿出一个值，然后
then the actual time so let's say I'm
然后是实际时间，所以我说
going to give it five seconds so now if
要给它五秒钟，所以现在如果
I have a look at this future not
我看看这个未来
completed yet still not completed and
完成但仍未完成，
now it completely normally and the value
现在它完全正常了，价值
is actually timed out so this is really
实际上是超时的，所以这真的
useful when you have sort of distributed
当您有一些分布式时很有用
computation let's say you have a
计算，假设您有一个
computation that involves talking to
涉及交谈的计算
several micro services and for each one
几个微服务，每个微服务
of those you want to express something
那些你想要表达的东西
like okay wait for this result from this
就像好吧，等待这个结果
micro service for five seconds if it
微服务五秒钟
completes that's fine if it doesn't
如果没有的话，可以完成
complete I'm going to load the default
完成，我将加载默认值
value or load the value from cache or
值或从缓存中加载值或
something like that you can also fail
这样的事情你也可能​​失败
the future if something doesn't complete
未完成的未来
in time I'm just going to reinitialize
及时我将要重新初始化
this here that's accomplished through
这是通过完成
the method or timeout which just takes
只是需要的方法或超时
time so I'll give it five seconds again
时间，所以我会再给它五秒钟
and now if I try to get the value it's
现在，如果我尝试获得价值，那就是
going to wait for five seconds and then
等五秒钟然后
it's going to fail with a timeout
它将因超时而失败
exception so these are sort of two
例外，所以这是两个
methods that allow you to express time
表示时间的方法
dependencies
依存关系
the final method that I wanted to talk
我想谈的最后一种方法
about here is the method copy and copy
关于这里是方法复制和复制
essentially allows you to create a
本质上允许您创建一个
defensive copy of a future so this is
未来的防御副本，所以这是
really useful when you're designing a
当您设计一个
synchronous api's where you're actually
同步api的实际位置
returning completable futures you want
返回您想要的可完成期货
the clients to be able to take these
客户能够接受这些
futures and respond to the changes in
期货和应对变化
these futures but you don't want them to
这些期货，但您不希望它们
be able to write back you don't want
能够回信你不想
them to be able to complete the future
他们能够完成未来
that you're using internally and that's
您在内部使用的那是
what copy does so it's kind of like a
复制什么，所以有点像
one-way synchronization and let's take a
单向同步，让我们
look at this let's reinitialize this
看看这个，让我们重新初始化
here and I'm going to create a copy
在这里，我要创建一个副本
let's call it a copy and then you can
我们称它为副本，然后您可以
see that none of them is completed yet
看到他们还没有完成
obviously if I complete the original the
显然，如果我完成了原始的
original is completed now and the copy
原件现已完成，副本
is completed as well so the change was
也完成了，所以更改是
propagated for the client to react so
传播给客户做出反应
what happens if I do added a very round
如果我增加一轮会怎样？
let's reinitialize CF reinitialize the
让我们重新初始化CF重新初始化
copy and now I'm going to complete the
复制，现在我要完成
copy here and copy is done the original
复制到此处并完成原始复制
didn't change so it's like a one-way
没有改变，所以就像单向
synchronization thing and that's that's
同步的东西，那就是
a really nice feature to have so I think
一个非常好的功能，所以我认为
it's going to be really useful so I
这将非常有用，所以我
think that's enough about these tiny
认为这些小东西就足够了
additions to existing api's let's have a
现有api的新增功能
look at some new ideas in Java 9 and the
看看Java 9和
first one on the list is stack poker
列表上的第一个是堆栈扑克
stuck poker gives us easy lazy and
卡住的扑克让我们容易懒惰，
stream friendly access to stack traces
流友好访问堆栈跟踪
so prior to Java 9 I could do something
所以在Java 9之前我可以做点什么
like this could have a frbel and call
像这样可能有一个fröbel和电话
the get stack trace method and this
获取堆栈跟踪方法和这个
gives me an array of stack trace
给我一个堆栈跟踪数组
elements so I print is here this is my
元素，所以我在这里打印这是我的
stack trace at this point in time there
此时的堆栈跟踪
are a few issues with this issue number
这个问题编号有几个问题
one this is pretty expensive it doesn't
一个，这是相当昂贵的，不是
matter whether I only the first few
不管我是否只有前几个
frames or the first few elements of the
框架或
stack trace the JVM always need to needs
JVM一直需要的堆栈跟踪
to eagerly capture the whole stack there
急切地捕获整个堆栈
are also no convenience methods account
也没有方便的方法帐号
easily filter
轻松过滤
out I can easily get access to the
我可以轻松访问
actual class instances of the classes
类的实际类实例
that declared the methods and on top of
声明了方法并在
that I cannot even rely on this stack
我什至不能依靠这个堆栈
trace to be complete the specification
跟踪以完成规格
says that JVM can omit certain elements
说JVM可以省略某些元素
if it helps performance thankfully all
如果它能帮助提高性能
these disadvantages are addressed in
这些缺点在
Java 9 through a class called stack
Java 9通过称为堆栈的类
Walker so stuck Walker is actually
沃克如此卡住沃克实际上是
pretty easy to use you can just obtain
相当容易使用，您可以获得
an instance here and the main method
这里的实例和主要方法
here is walk that allows me to access
这是允许我进入的步行
deck traces as streams so I can do
甲板痕迹作为溪流，所以我可以做
something like this I can collect this
这样的东西我可以收集
stream and just use collectors to a list
流并仅使用收集器到列表
and this gives me the full structure is
这给了我完整的结构是
very similar to the one that we got from
与我们从中获得的非常相似
the get sectaries method however in this
get sectaries方法，但是在此
case I can take advantage of all the
情况下，我可以利用所有
stream operations so if I was only
流操作，所以如果我只是
interested in stack trace of that tree
对那棵树的堆栈跟踪感兴趣
for example I could just do a limit tree
例如我可以做一个极限树
this just gives me the top three
这只给了我前三名
elements of the stack I can also easily
堆栈的元素我也可以轻松地
get access to to the class instances you
可以访问您的类实例
can install the stack driver to retain
可以安装堆栈驱动程序以保留
the references and then I'm just going
参考，然后我就去
to remove this limit here I'm gonna use
在这里删除这个限制
a map to extract this information so
地图以提取此信息，因此
I'll do for each frame
我会为每一帧做
give me the declaring class and these
给我宣讲课，这些
are all the classes involving a stack
所有涉及堆栈的类
trace so it's really nice it's it's a
跟踪，所以真的很好，它是一个
great convenience API to have in Java
Java中非常方便的API
another API I'm really excited about and
我真的很兴奋的另一个API
I think it's actually probably the most
我认为这实际上可能是最
underrated feature in Java 9 for me
对我而言Java 9中的功能被低估了
personally is the process handle API so
个人是流程处理API，所以
the new process handle API allows me to
新的流程句柄API使我能够
easily get information about processes
轻松获取有关流程的信息
so what we had available in Java prior
所以我们以前在Java中可用的东西
to Java 9 since gentleman 5 actually was
Java 9，因为先生5实际上是
the process builder API that made it
实现它的流程构建器API
really easy to launch external processes
非常容易启动外部流程
so I could do something like this
所以我可以做这样的事情
process builder
流程建设者
and I forgot to close this command let's
我忘了关闭这个命令
say I want to list all the Java
说我要列出所有Java
processes in my system it's going to do
我系统中的流程
JPS start and this starts an external
JPS启动，这将启动一个外部
process JPS now the main limitation of
现在处理JPS的主要限制是
this API is that I cannot get any
这个API是我什么也得不到
information about the process even
关于过程的信息甚至
really simple things such as the PID
非常简单的东西，例如PID
that's available in Java 9 but it wasn't
在Java 9中可用，但不是
easy to access before the dish so what
容易在菜之前进入
people ended up doing is either using
人们最终做的是要么使用
jmx which is really hacky or they would
jmx真的很hacky，否则他们会
write their own tools so typically you
写他们自己的工具，所以通常你
would call something like a PS and grab
会叫PS之类的东西抢
and it would essentially obtain
它实际上将获得
information about the process from the
有关该过程的信息
outside which is just really unnecessary
外面真的没有必要
tedious to write not to mention all the
写作乏味，更何况
portability issues so it's really great
可移植性问题，所以真的很棒
to see this finally resolved as part of
看到这最终解决了
the JDK so JDK 9 provides an interface
JDK，因此JDK 9提供了一个接口
called process handle which allows me to
称为过程句柄，它使我能够
get all sorts of information about the
获得有关
actual process so I can obtain a handle
实际的过程，所以我可以获得一个句柄
to my current process and there I can
到我当前的流程，在那里我可以
easily extract the PID just like this I
像这样我很容易提取PID
can also get access to all sorts of
还可以访问各种
other information through the info
通过信息的其他信息
interface you can see this gives me
界面，您可以看到这给了我
quite a few things and there's kind of
相当多的东西，还有一种
convenience methods for everything so I
一切方便的方法，所以我
think once that it's going to be used
一旦考虑将要使用
pretty frequently it's common line which
这是很常见的
essentially tells you how your java
本质上告诉您您的Java
application was launched so it's the
应用程序已启动，因此
full full Java command all the arguments
完整的完整Java命令的所有参数
everything so that's really useful you
一切，这对您真的很有用
can also get information about other
也可以获取有关其他信息
processes in your system so I can do can
系统中的进程，因此我可以
do something like process handle all
做类似处理所有事情
processes which gives me a stream and
给我一个流的过程
then I can extract some information from
然后我可以从中提取一些信息
this let's say for each process give me
假设每个过程都给我
info and then the command and then I'm
信息，然后命令，然后我
just going to collect this
只是要收集这个
and this gives me all the commands
这给了我所有的命令
running in my system another really
在我的系统中运行另一个
useful part of this API that's new in
这个API的新功能
Java 9 is method on exit which allows
Java 9是退出方法，它允许
you to essentially trigger an action
您本质上触发动作
when an external process completes and
当外部流程完成时，
that's that's really useful so let's try
那真的很有用，所以让我们尝试
something here I'm just going to create
我将在这里创建一些东西
a process that has predictable run time
运行时间可预测的过程
so let's call let's go sleep for example
例如，让我们打电话入睡
I'm going to tell it sleep for 3 seconds
我要告诉它睡觉三秒钟
and I can just start the process and
我可以开始这个过程
immediately obtain the handle to it
立即获得它的句柄
and then I can call the method on exit
然后我可以在退出时调用该方法
which gives me the completable future
这给了我无限的未来
and we've seen the API for computable
我们已经看到了可计算的API
futures I can easily just do something
期货我可以轻松地做点什么
like then accept and there I will just
就像然后接受，我在那里
print I can just print the whole process
打印我可以打印整个过程
handle actually so the two string
实际上处理两个字符串
they're essentially prints the PID so
他们实质上是打印PID，因此
just to recap what I'm expecting to
只是概括我的期望
happen here is a process starts a
发生在这里是一个过程开始
synchronously and then three seconds
同步然后三秒钟
later I'm going to see the PID of the
稍后，我将看到
now-deceased process straight it's here
现在已经死了的流程就在这里
process started and now I can see the
过程开始了，现在我可以看到
PID so that's really useful and I also
PID，这真的很有用，我也
don't need to limit myself to managing
不需要将自己局限于管理
individual processes I can build the
我可以建立的个别流程
whole pipelines in the sense of UNIX
UNIX上的整个管道
pipelines so I can express things like
管道，这样我就可以表达
take the output of this first process
获取第一个过程的输出
and connect it to the input of the next
并将其连接到下一个的输入
process let's just demonstrate this
过程让我们来演示一下
really quickly let's say I'm gonna last
很快我就说我要走了
all my java processes and then wrapped
我所有的Java进程，然后包装
for J shell which obviously should be
对于J shell，显然应该是
running at this point so I can get us
在这一点上运行，所以我可以得到我们
create a process builder here and to use
在此处创建流程生成器并使用
my favorite JPS
我最喜欢的JPS
and I'm gonna to call it Jake yes and
我会叫它杰克是的，
then I will just call collagraph for J
那我就给Collagraph打电话给J
shell and let's call this grep and then
外壳，我们称这个grep然后
I can just throw these as a pipeline so
我可以将它们作为管道丢弃，这样
I'll just do start pipeline and you can
我只是开始做管道，你可以
see that this takes a list of process
看到这需要过程列表
builders so I can take advantage of the
建设者，所以我可以利用
convenience factory methods here
这里的便利工厂方法
I'm just going to do a list of JPS and
我将列出一份JPS，
grab so let's call this pipeline so now
抢，让我们现在叫这个管道
this is started synchronously if I try
如果我尝试，这将同步启动
to access it now it should be finished
现在访问它应该完成
and you can see that everything finish
你会看到一切都完成了
correctly with the zero return value so
正确地与零返回值，所以
now let's try and take a look at what I
现在让我们尝试看看我的
actually ended up processing so I'm
实际上结束了处理，所以我
going to take the pipeline here and get
将在这里采取管道并获得
access to the last process in the list
访问列表中的最后一个进程
which is index 1 and then I will obtain
这是索引1，然后我将获得
an inlet stream to the output of the
入口流到
process
处理
I need to do the whole Java boilerplate
我需要做整个Java样板
loop here so I'll just let this in an
循环在这里，所以我就让它
input stream reader and I made a typo
输入流阅读器，我打错了字
like this and then rub this in a
这样，然后在一个
bufferedreader and then finally I can
bufferedreader，最后我可以
use the method read line
使用方法读取行
typo anywhere
到处都是错字
oh here yeah thank you and I can see
哦，是的，谢谢，我可以看到
that it found the process with this PID
它使用此PID找到了进程
that's called a shell tool provider
称为外壳工具提供程序
which is the actual process that runs
这是实际运行的过程
through a shell so that's very nice and
通过外壳，这非常好，
you can see how this is a real powerful
您可以看到这是多么强大
API and it's something that you wouldn't
API，这是您不会想要的
want to implement yourself especially in
想要实现自己，尤其是在
a way that works on all the different
一种适用于所有不同方式的方式
platforms so it's really great to see
平台，所以真的很高兴看到
this as part of the JDK now the last
这是JDK的一部分，现在是最后一个
feature that I wanted to talk about here
我想在这里谈论的功能
is the new HTTP to client and yeah lots
是新的客户端和HTTP协议
of questions at the end
最后的问题
Thanks so the new HTTP client not only
谢谢，所以新的HTTP客户端不仅
provides a much cleaner API than the old
提供了比旧版本更干净的API
HTTP URL connection but it also supports
HTTP URL连接，但它也支持
all the cool new things
所有很棒的新事物
it supports HTTP to WebSockets TLS and
它支持HTTP到WebSockets TLS和
everything that will expect server push
期望服务器推送的一切
cookies proxies synchronous requests
Cookies代理同步请求
that kind of thing new HTTP client API
那种新的HTTP客户端API
is delivered as an incubator module in
作为孵化器模块交付
Gemini which means that it's not
双子座意味着不是
completely finalized and it's not
完全敲定，不是
resolved by default and lives in a
默认情况下已解决，并位于
special namespace but I pre imported
特殊名称空间，但我已预先导入
here into J shell so that we can play
在这里进入J shell，以便我们可以玩
around with it now to demonstrate the
现在围绕它来演示
client functionality I'm going to need a
客户端功能，我需要一个
server and if there's anything that
服务器，如果有什么
we've learned from previous demos at
我们从以前的演示中学到了
this conference is that you cannot rely
这个会议是你不能依靠
on the internet here so I'm just going
在这里的互联网上，所以我就去
to write a really quick one here in Java
用Java在这里写一个非常快速的
and actually really like this example
真的很喜欢这个例子
because I think this is something that
因为我认为这是
people usually consider hard to do or
人们通常认为很难做或
they assume that it's going to require a
他们认为这将需要一个
lot of code in Java but actually you can
Java中的很多代码，但实际上您可以
create a very simple server very easily
轻松创建一个非常简单的服务器
just using functionality provided in the
仅使用
JDK and it's all the API that has been
JDK及其所有的API
around for a very long time so I will
周围很长一段时间，所以我会
just create the simplest possible server
只需创建最简单的服务器
there's going to be one endpoint that
会有一个端点
just returns a fixed string so let's
只是返回一个固定的字符串，所以让我们
start by creating an HTTP handler for
首先为创建HTTP处理程序
this endpoint I'm going to call it a
这个端点，我将其称为
handler that's going to take an HTTP
将采用HTTP的处理程序
exchange as a quick lambda here so I
在这里交换为快速lambda，所以我
will define the string that I want to
将定义我想要的字符串
use let's call it body it's going to be
用它来称呼它的身体
hello Java 1 and now I will set the
您好Java 1，现在我将设置
response headers I'm always going to
我总是去响应头
respond with 200 everything is ok I'm
以200回应，一切正常
going to attach the length of my string
要附加我的弦的长度
here and finally I will ride the string
在这里，最后我会骑弦
to the output so I will open an output
到输出，所以我将打开一个输出
stream here let's assign the response
流在这里，让我们分配响应
body here and too many brackets no it
身体在这里，括号太多了
looks fine and there I will just provide
看起来不错，我将在那里提供
to this output stream and I have to do
到这个输出流，我必须做
this through get bytes because it's an
通过获取字节，因为这是一个
old API but that's ok for demo purposes
旧的API，但可以进行演示
and now I will just close everything
现在我将关闭所有内容
great so if you take a look here this is
太好了，所以如果您在这里看看
our new handler looks ok so we can go on
我们的新处理程序看起来还不错，所以我们可以继续
and try to start a server so I'm going
并尝试启动服务器，所以我要
to create a server here and this takes a
在这里创建服务器，这需要一个
port so I will give it let's say 8,000
端口，所以我给它说8,000
and don't need a backlog let's call this
不需要积压，我们称之为
HS and then I will create the end point
HS，然后我将创建终点
let's say slash hello and I will touch
比方说，您好，我会碰
my favorite handler to this and now
我现在最喜欢的处理程序
finally I can start a server so
终于我可以启动服务器了
hopefully the server is running and to
希望服务器正在运行并
test this let's use the old HTTP URL
测试一下，让我们使用旧的HTTP URL
connection API just to see how how ugly
只是看连接API怎么丑
it was and how good the new client looks
那是什么，新客户看起来如何
in comparison so I will start by
相比之下，我将从
defining a URI here it's going to point
在这里定义一个URI
to my local server so it's HTTP
到我的本地服务器，所以它是HTTP
localhost 8080 RI then I will convert
localhost 8080 RI然后我将转换
this to a URL so that I can open a
这到一个URL，以便我可以打开一个
connection here and this actually
连接在这里，这实际上
returns your auto connection which is no
返回您的自动连接，否
good I actually want HTTP royal
好，我实际上想要HTTP Royal
connection and this whole API was
连接，整个API是
designed with multiple protocols in mind
设计时考虑了多种协议
even though HTTP is realistically the
即使HTTP实际上是
only one that you would use so
您只会使用一个
unfortunately I need to
不幸的是我需要
this here so I'm just going to do HTTP
这个在这里，所以我只是要做HTTP
URL connection let's call it C so you
URL连接我们称之为C
can see that I'm just starting out and
可以看到我才刚开始
this API is already really ugly now I
我现在这个API已经很丑了
can specify the request method it's just
可以指定只是请求方法
going to be a simple cut and this needs
将是一个简单的削减，这需要
to be passed as fast as a string again
再次像字符串一样快地传递
not really nice no let's test if this
不太好，不，我们来测试一下
works
作品
so do you get response code and I can
那你得到响应码，我可以
say that it's 200 that looks promising
说200看起来很有希望
so let's try and read the actual output
因此，让我们尝试读取实际输出
and again we need to do the standard
再一次，我们需要做标准
Java boilerplate stuff I will open we
Java样板资料，我将打开我们
will get the input stream from my
将从我的输入流
connection rub this in an input stream
连接在输入流中摩擦
reader I brought this in the
读者我把这个带进了
bufferedreader a lot of boilerplate here
缓冲的阅读器在这里很多样板
and I can finally read the line that
我终于可以读到
says how much I want so that's great now
说我想要多少，所以现在很棒
let's try to do this with the new HTTP
让我们尝试使用新的HTTP执行此操作
to a client so though the new API is
给客户，所以尽管新的API是
kind of built around three main classes
围绕三个主要类别构建
there's HTTP client HTTP request and
有一个HTTP客户端HTTP请求，
HTTP response pretty self-explanatory so
HTTP响应相当不言自明，因此
just start by creating the client here
只是从这里创建客户端开始
in HTTP client and let's call this a
在HTTP客户端中，我们称其为
client then I will construct the request
客户，然后我将构建请求
which uses a builder pattern here so
在这里使用构建器模式
I'll just obtain a builder give it your
我会请一位建筑商给你
URI that I had from before specify the
我之前来自的URI指定
get method as a method this is really
get方法作为一种方法，这真的
nice and then build it let's call this a
好，然后建立它，我们称之为
request and then I can finally send the
请求，然后我最终可以发送
request to my server so this takes a
请求到我的服务器，所以这需要一个
request and something called body
请求和所谓的身体
handler here and I just want to tell it
处理程序在这里，我只想告诉它
in this case to treat everything as a
在这种情况下，将一切视为
string and thank for there's a building
字符串，并感谢有一个建筑物
handler for this so I will just do body
这个的处理程序，所以我会做身体
handler
处理程序
a string let's call this response and
一个字符串，我们称这个响应为
now I can easily obtain information from
现在我可以轻松地从
this response I can just do response
这个回应我就可以回应
status code 200 response body hello
状态码200响应主体您好
gentlemen
先生们
it just really nice really clean and
真的很好很干净
it's really flexible as well if I wanted
如果我想要的话，它也非常灵活
to make this synchronous all that I need
使这个同步所有我需要的
to do is change this send a sink and
要做的就是更改此发送接收器和
this would return completable future
这将返回可完成的未来
here let's just use this wait
在这里，让我们使用这个等待
okay one more time
好，再等一次
let's call this a response and yeah that
我们称之为回应，是的，
looks good actually and now this gives
实际上看起来不错，现在这给
me a computable feature we've seen this
我有一个可计算的功能，我们已经看到了
API before so I can just call it cat and
之前的API，所以我可以将其称为cat和
then body here it is I think as I watch
然后身体就在这里
all one so that's really nice they also
所有这一切真的很好，他们也
have really nice handling around TLS
对TLS的处理非常好
that goes way beyond scope of this talk
这超出了本演讲的范围
but you can do all sorts of things like
但您可以做各种各样的事情，例如
managing certificates and all that you
管理证书以及您的全部
know very nice way and that's basically
知道非常好的方法，基本上
it that's the overview of my favorite
这是我最喜欢的概述
API is in Java 9 so I hope you found
API是Java 9中的API，所以希望您能找到
this interesting
这个有趣
before we go since I don't have any
我们走之前，因为我没有任何东西
slides I will just save this session
幻灯片，我将只保存此会话
save the history of this session to a
将此会话的历史记录保存到
file let's say backup J shell and I can
文件说备份J Shell，我可以
post this video later if you want to
如果您想稍后发布此视频
come back to some of these examples and
回到这些例子中，
that's pretty much it so we're close to
差不多了，所以我们接近
running out of time but we have some
时间用完了，但我们有一些
time for questions but regardless I'll
是时候提问了，但无论如何
be around until the next talk starts so
一直待到下一个谈话开始，所以
thank you and enjoy the rest of Taiwan
谢谢你，喜欢台湾其他地区
[Applause]
[掌声]